fearlessmotivation.com 2018-12-27

# Privacy Policy - Fearless Motivation - Motivational Videos & Music

Your privacy is of utmost importance to FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd).  This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) collects, and the ways in which FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) uses that personal information.

This privacy policy has been compiled to better serve those who are concerned with how their ‘Personally Identifiable Information’ (PII) is being used online. PII, as described in US privacy law and information security, is information that can be used on its own or with other information to identify, contact, or locate a single person, or to identify an individual in context. Please read our privacy policy carefully to get a clear understanding of how we collect, use, protect or otherwise handle your Personally Identifiable Information in accordance with our website.

Policy key definitions:

•”I”, “our”, “us”, or “we” refer to the business, [Business name & other trading names].

•”you”, “the user” refer to the person(s) using this website.

•GDPR means General Data Protection Act.

•PECR means Privacy & Electronic Communications Regulation.

•ICO means Information Commissioner’s Office.

•Cookies mean small files stored on a users computer or device.

Processing of your personal data

Under the GDPR (General Data Protection Regulation) we control and / or process any personal information about you electronically using the following lawful bases.

•We are exempt from registration in the ICO Data Protection Register because this business operates outside of the EU

•Lawful basis: Consent

•Data retention period: We will continue to process your information under this basis until you withdraw consent or it is determined your consent no longer exists.

**Personal information collection**

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

  * information about your use of this website;
  * information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;
  * information about transactions carried out over this website;
  * information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and
  * any other information that you send to FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd).

**Using personal information**

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) may use your personal information to:

  * [administer this website;]
  * [personalize the website for you;]
  * [enable your access to and use of the website services;]
  * [publish information about you on the website;]
  * [send to you products that you purchase;]
  * [supply to you services that you purchase;]
  * [send to you statements and invoices;]
  * [collect payments from you; and]
  * [send you marketing communications.]

**Additional Service Partners**

We may use the following third-party service providers named below to process and store your data:

Mailchimp (The Rocket Science Group, LLC), which we use to manage email marketing subscriber lists and send emails to our subscribers.

Mailchimp’s Privacy Policy & Cookie Policy can be found under _Resources & further information_

Where FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

Does our site allow third-party behavioral tracking? It is important to note that we allow third-party behavioral tracking

**Your individual rights**

Under the GDPR your rights are as follows. You can read more about [your rights in details here](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-the-general-data-protection-regulation-gdpr/individual-rights/);

•the right to be informed;

•the right of access;

•the right to rectification;

•the right to erasure;

•the right to restrict processing;

•the right to data portability;

•the right to object; and

•the right not to be subject to automated decision-making including profiling.

You also have the right to complain to the ICO [[www.ico.org.uk](http://www.ico.org.uk/)] if you feel there is a problem with the way we are handling your data.

We handle subject access requests in accordance with the GDPR.

**Securing your data**

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.]

Your personal information is contained behind secured networks and is only accessible by a limited number of persons who have special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential. In addition, all sensitive/credit information you supply is encrypted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology.

We implement a variety of security measures when a user enters, submits, or accesses their information to maintain the safety of your personal information.

Our methods meet the GDPR compliance requirement.

**Cross-border data transfers**

Information that FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

**Do we use ‘cookies’?**

Yes. Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computer’s hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the site’s or service provider’s systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information. For instance, we use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart. They are also used to help us understand your preferences based on previous or current site activity, which enables us to provide you with improved services. We also use cookies to help us compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.

We use cookies to:

• Understand and save user’s preferences for future visits.

• Keep track of advertisements.

• Compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interactions in order to offer better site experiences and tools in the future. We may also use trusted third-party services that track this information on our behalf.

You can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies. You do this through your browser settings. Since browser is a little different, look at your browser’s Help Menu to learn the correct way to modify your cookies.

If you turn cookies off, It won’t affect the user’s experience .

**Google**

Google’s advertising requirements can be summed up by Google’s Advertising Principles. They are put in place to provide a positive experience for users. <https://support.google.com/adwordspolicy/answer/1316548?hl=en> 

We use Google AdSense Advertising on our website.

Google, as a third-party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on previous visits to our site and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt-out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google Ad and Content Network privacy policy.

We have implemented the following:

• Remarketing with Google AdSense

• Google Display Network Impression Reporting

• Demographics and Interests Reporting

• DoubleClick Platform Integration

We, along with third-party vendors such as Google use first-party cookies (such as the Google Analytics cookies) and third-party cookies (such as the DoubleClick cookie) or other third-party identifiers together to compile data regarding user interactions with ad impressions and other ad service functions as they relate to our website.

Opting out:

Users can set preferences for how Google advertises to you using the Google Ad Settings page. Alternatively, you can opt out by visiting the Network Advertising Initiative Opt Out page or by using the Google Analytics Opt Out Browser add on.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act**

CalOPPA is the first state law in the nation to require commercial websites and online services to post a privacy policy. The law’s reach stretches well beyond California to require any person or company in the United States (and conceivably the world) that operates websites collecting Personally Identifiable Information from California consumers to post a conspicuous privacy policy on its website stating exactly the information being collected and those individuals or companies with whom it is being shared. – See more at: <http://consumercal.org/california-online-privacy-protection-act-caloppa/#sthash.0FdRbT51.dpuf>

According to CalOPPA, we agree to the following:

Users can visit our site anonymously.

Once this privacy policy is created, we will add a link to it on our home page or as a minimum, on the first significant page after entering our website.

Our Privacy Policy link includes the word ‘Privacy’ and can easily be found on the page specified above.

**CAN SPAM Act**

The CAN-SPAM Act is a law that sets the rules for commercial email, establishes requirements for commercial messages, gives recipients the right to have emails stopped from being sent to them, and spells out tough penalties for violations.

We collect your email address in order to:

• Send information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions

• Market to our mailing list or continue to send emails to our clients after the original transaction has occurred.

To be in accordance with CANSPAM, we agree to the following:

• Not use false or misleading subjects or email addresses.

• Identify the message as an advertisement in some reasonable way.

• Include the physical address of our business or site headquarters.

• Monitor third-party email marketing services for compliance, if one is used.

• Honor opt-out/unsubscribe requests quickly.

• Allow users to unsubscribe by using the link at the bottom of each email.

If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, you can email us at team@fearlessmotivation.com or;

• Follow the instructions at the bottom of each email.

and we will promptly remove you from ALL correspondence.

**COPPA (Children Online Privacy Protection Act)**

When it comes to the collection of personal information from children under the age of 13 years old, the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act (COPPA) puts parents in control. The Federal Trade Commission, United States’ consumer protection agency, enforces the COPPA Rule, which spells out what operators of websites and online services must do to protect children’s privacy and safety online.

We do not specifically market to children under the age of 13 years old.

**Fair Information Practices**

The Fair Information Practices Principles form the backbone of privacy law in the United States and the concepts they include have played a significant role in the development of data protection laws around the globe. Understanding the Fair Information Practice Principles and how they should be implemented is critical to comply with the various privacy laws that protect personal information.

In order to be in line with Fair Information Practices we will take the following responsive action, should a data breach occur:

We will notify you via email

• Within 7 business days

We also agree to the Individual Redress Principle which requires that individuals have the right to legally pursue enforceable rights against data collectors and processors who fail to adhere to the law. This principle requires not only that individuals have enforceable rights against data users, but also that individuals have recourse to courts or government agencies to investigate and/or prosecute non-compliance by data processors.

**Updating this statement**

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

**Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd) is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

**Resources & further information**

•[Overview of the GDPR – General Data Protection Regulation](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/data-protection-reform/overview-of-the-gdpr/)

•[Data Protection Act 1998](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/ukpga/1998/29/contents)

•[Privacy and Electronic Communications Regulations 2003](http://www.legislation.gov.uk/uksi/2003/2426/contents/made)

•[The Guide to the PECR 2003](https://ico.org.uk/for-organisations/guide-to-pecr/)

•[Twitter Privacy Policy](http://twitter.com/privacy)

•[Facebook Privacy Policy](http://www.facebook.com/about/privacy/)

•[Google Privacy Policy](http://www.google.com/privacy.html)

•[Mailchimp Privacy Policy](http://mailchimp.com/legal/privacy/)

•[Mailchimp Cookie Policy](https://mailchimp.com/legal/cookies/?_ga=2.10730740.1733339234.1526943180-971653740.1526624483)

**Contact  FearlessMotivation.com (Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd)**

If you have any questions regarding this privacy policy, would like to update your personal information or have an enquiry about the treatment of your personal information, please write:

  * by email to team@fearlessmotivation.com; or
  * by post to Fearless Motivation Pty Ltd – PO BOX 5324, Robina Town Centre, QLD, 4230 – Australia
